

## **Amenti Emiru**

**Phone:** 0964196015

Address: Addis Ababa, Ethiopia
Email: amentidan14@gmail.com

Quick learner with academic abilities and technical knowledge to succeed in different roles. Ready to expand horizons with additional knowledge and abilities gained from training and experience. Always ready to help others and use abilities to support team goals.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **School Charity Club**

September 2018 - June 2020

#### Volunteer

- Picked up additional tasks to aid team success.
- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.
- Developed ongoing programmes using good team communication and collaboration.

Student Council September 2018- May 2019

#### Member

- Arranging and coordinating events.
- Performing public speech in the class.
- Managing and facilitating methods to resolve students problem.

## **Ethiopia Red Cross Society**

September 2018- May 2019

### Member

- Attended in-person and online training to learn about volunteer roles, safety requirements and organisational goals.
- Maintained excellent professional relationships by going extra mile to complete tasks voluntarily.
- Focused volunteering efforts on supporting and expanding community-based work to meet needs of local residents.

### **EDUCATION**

## Kiltu Kara Secondary School

Grade 9 and 10

## **Nekemet Primary School**

Grade 11

# **Bethel Academy School**

Grade 12 (high school diploma)

### SKILLS

- Problem solving skill
- Communication skill
- Troubleshooting
- Google workspace
- Leadership skill

### **LANGUAGES**

Amharic (Native ), English (Fluent ), Afan oromo (Fluent )